Eamon Travers

Developer

www.eamontravers.dev

Eamon Travers

Lichtenraderstr. 55 Berlin, 12049

eamon.trav@gmail.com

English: Native Deutsch: B2 spoken/C1 written



About

Skills

I'm a developer, mathematician and lifetime learner.

From Ireland, in Berlin since 2020. Professional experience includes working as a dev, logistics coordinator and MD.

Advanced Intermediate Junior Basic Experience

Typescript/Javascript, Python, React, HTML5, CSS, NextJS, UI/UX

AWS, SQL, Git, SCSS, Dynamic Programming, Data Structures, Algorithms, Testing, SEO, NodeJS, Figma, ORM

Jest, Redux, Angular, Selenium, Photoshop

Java, Go, Vue, Java, Go, WebSockets

English: Native Deutsch: B2 spoken/C1 written

Experience

Developer /

- Currently building software/SPAs for the Western Australia CMN.
- Custom website creation (NextJs) striving for best practices and current tech usage (generative AI, SSR/SSG/interleaving/performance balancing).
- Full-stack development for personal and client projects.

Austral Travel / Programme + Logistics Co-ord. / 2021 - 2023, BERLIN

- Led on-the-ground coordination for MBA & EMBA programmes from top business universities like the Cambridge & Harvard Business Schools.



PAS / Digital Audio Engineer / 2020 - 2021, BERLIN

- Managed audio (and often lighting) for international artists and government-funded installation pieces in an esteemed art space on the Spree.

Common Grounds Co. / Vice-Chair/Prod.

Manager/Co-Founder/ 2016 - 2019, DUBLIN

- Founded and led a successful Artists' collective.
- Creative and Technical director for core events, including slots at all major Irish festivals & flying 8200 km to put on a festival in Parkfield, California.

Education

Online / Learning on the job /

2020 - 2024 , Berlin

- Computer Science, Software Engineering, Web Development
- Immersion, digestion, implementation, testing, repeat. Ask me anything!

Maynooth University / B.A Dual Honors Mathematics & Music Technologies

2012 - 2016, Maynooth, Ireland

First class honours. Academic Scholarship recipient.

Other

I am a tinkerer and a questioner at heart, and am never happy sitting still. I try to bring passion to every undertaking, but rely on my maths background to apply rigour throughout. When I'm not working, I love playing chess in Berlin (top 2% globally on chess.com), cooking for friends and playing music. I'm looking for a job that is fulfilling and mentally engaging to provide a rock to structure my life around!

Thank you for your time.

Kind regards

Area sel